为了在应用中向OpenWeatherMap请求数据，
To fetch the data from OpenWeatherMap within an
首先我们需要以之前确定的URL的形式，
app, first we need to make an HTTP request to the
向API发送一个HTTP请求。
API at the URL that we decided on earlier. Then we
然后我们需要从输入流中以JSON字符串的形式读取响应。
need to read the response from the input stream to get
它还没有被解析，不过我们稍后再来了解这方面的知识。
a JSON string. It hasn't been parsed yet, but we'll worry
接下来，我们需要通过断开连接并且关闭所有输入流
about that later. Then we clean up by disconnecting the connection
来进行清理工作。我们也记录错误日志。
and closing any input streams. We also log any errors that
由于网络处理的部分有非常多样板化的代码，
we catch. Since it's a lot of networking boiler plate code,
我们将为您提供的这些功能
we've provided you with a code snippet
的代码片段。请参阅下方的
that handles these steps. See the link for
GitHub链接的简介。当你看完以后，
the GitHub gist below. After you've taken a
点击此框，继续往下学习。
look at it, check this box to continue.